This is the Japanese Cuisine Academy
platfform that I had the opportunity to
develop during my permanent contract at Soft
Concept. The platform is a
bilingual e-learning app
so French, English at destination
of sushi machine users
that are designed by Sushi
Robots. There are 4 types of profiles
on the application, so Sushi Robots which
will be the administrator of the
training to use the machines.
There will be the signs, so by
Sushi Shop et cetera, the
sites by brand, so for example the
Sushi Shop in the Cours Vitton
in Lyon and finally the last,
The last profile will be the
employees, i.e. employees who
use machines that are trained
via the platform. If I
connects as Sushi Robots.
So I have access to the clients, to the board
and modules. So if I access
to the customers, I will have the
company name, so the name by
example Côté Sushi, the manager email,
the manager name,
the maximum number of users, the maximum per
institution and institution name. If
for example I add a client Test
I'm seeing what is
mandatory, Fast Food by
example. The maximum number of users
by shop, then
the email
test@gmail.com
we don't send the notification and a
user ID. In fact, what is happening
is that the customer, therefore,
the brand will receive a code
user to be able to log in
to the application.
So we'll be able to edit
customer information. One
will be able to add a establishment
in this company, by
example, Test Paris for example,
the country, the SIRET, the address, the
main information and email.
Once again,
we can delete
the customer. And we can also
list the machines that are going to be
used by this brand,
so the machines, the entirety
of the machines from Sushi Robots
that are available, therefore
for example, the Oshibori machine.
So here we have, an image of the
machine. After that, there are
different types of machines, there are the
sushi machines, maki machines, et
cetera. Gyosa machines,
then the dashboard. In the dashboard,
there will be the indicators, so
there, for example, a global view of
all the establishments. Therefore,
we will have, for example, the possibility
to extract the information in CSV, therefore
the number of registrants in all the
establishments (7 for instance). So there,
it's going to be on the entire cost of
all customers
combined, the overall average scores per
establishment, the distribution of
registered people by institution.
We're going to see the modules, so the modules.
For example, the module on the ASM865 machine
which is a sushi machine. The
number of questions. In fact,
we're actually going to be able to import a
zip archive which contains the
questionnaire and which, after deployment,
will act as
a survey.
This is the subject of the module in French,
English and the zip archive with
the number of questions.
If I log out and log in
as a
customer therefore a brand (for example,
Sushi
Shop).
So, I have access to the
establishments, therefore all the brands,
Sushi Shop sites, the table of
the indicators, the guide
and contact. So the
user guide,so for example there,
it's going to be the JCA guide,
here is Japan Food Solutions so
a manual with the catalogue and
use of the platform.
So the establishments, there will be
for example, the name of
the establishment, the address, the city,
same principle. So it's
really hierarchical. We will be able to
edit information, on
will be able to add
an employee.
We will be able to be
log in to follow the
trainings. Knowing that the training,
what is it going to be? It's going to be
investigations. So there will be MCQs, there will be
videos and there will be
also images. So, we can add a
establishment. There you have it, we can add
a collaborator and we can delete
the establishment. Then, Dashboard,
we'll see the level monitoring,
so we'll be able to know what
collaborator got, what grade,
when he participated and a recap sheet.
We will have the indicators for the
employee, so which employee has
spent, how long, on which module and
the average score he/she obtained.
And the contact so we will be able to
contact Sushi Robots
with email address and phone number
like a classic email.
So now if I log in like
Sushi Shop Vitton which is a site of
Sushi Shop.
So, now I'll be able to access
to employees, to have the
indicators,
the user guide and the
contact. So, the employees.
We will see Francis
Roger, Hélène Vitard, Maria Tipo with the
telephone, email. One
will be able to modify the
information.
So, each time, there is only email.
It is mandatory to be able to receive
so the link and we'll have to
enter the code each time that is
to be able to connect to the
platform. So remove the
collaborator :
each person who is going to use
the platform, which will follow the
training. So there, for example, the
global indicators, we will have the
number of hours they have spent.
So there, it's going to be really filtered
on employees.
After the distribution by category, then
NPS (insufficient, favourable, average),
distribution of tests by employee
and for each module. So, we're going to
to be able to filter and finally the last
profile that is
Francis Roger, associate at Sushi
Shop Vitton. So of course it's
sites, it's people. Sorry, it's
fake people. Therefore,
Francis Roger,
there the employee will
have access to its
training, so as
to be autonomous. The
training, assess your level and have
training that meets its
questions. So practical and
theoretical questions.
So, access my training.
So now I'm going to have all the
machines.
So there, for example, there is only one, for example,
for the Sushi Shop Vitton, there will be
have only this machine that is going to be
selected so we'll be able to
access, have a description of the
machine, how run through the
formation? There will be a minute, a
one-minute video for introduction, 1 MCQ
10-minute final, et cetera, and
we will be able to access it. We show how
we're going to get our feet back in the machine
and in which order.
And at the end, there's a little test then
for example, the test is in
English, I put
randomly.
End of the test,
end of the module.
After that, we have the indicators, so the
how many tests,
for how long, the
average score obtained and the
distribution of tests by month, time
passed by test on each module and the
scores per test.
We will disconnect.